A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Photographs, 1956-2003
  - Wallace, Richard D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Walsh, Raymond V., Jr., Undated (Box 31)
  - Walters, Frank S., Undated (Box 31)
  - Walters, Harry N., 1981 (Box 31)
  - Walters, Johnnie M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Walton, Albion W., Jr., 1969 (Box 31)
  - Walton, Edmund L., Jr., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Ware, Dr. Henry, Undated (Box 31)
  - Warkentin, James B., 1991 (Box 31)
  - Warne, Robin J., Undated (Box 31)
  - Warner, Christopher, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Warner, John W., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Warrington, Bernice, Undated (Box 31)
  - Washington Flyer Bus, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Waters, Douglas G., Undated (Box 31)
  - Waters, Susan, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Watson, Larry P., Undated (Box 31)
  - Watt, R.D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Watts, Dan - Dan Watts House of Carpets, Undated (Box 31)
  - Watts, George M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Watts, Ronald D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Weakley, Robert L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Weaver, Peggy, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Webb, John C., Undated (Box 31)
  - Webdale, Walter, Undated (Box 31)
  - Weber, Donald, Undated (Box 31)
  - Webster, Joanne M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wehner, Harrison, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Weickhardt, Karl F., Undated (Box 31)
  - Weigel, Lillian, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Weihe, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 31)
  - Weikel, M. Keith, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Weinberg, Robert, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Weinberger, Caspar - House on Ballantrae Farm Road, Undated (Box 31)
  - Weinstein, Susan, Undated (Box 31)
  - Weir, Charles J., 1986 (Box 31)
  - Welch, Capt. Glenn, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Welch, Roger J., Undated (Box 31)
  - Welk, Robert L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wellker, Robert D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Welsh, Bishop Thomas J, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wenger, Kenneth J., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wenk, Dr. Walter R., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wentz, Larry, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Werner, Braynard H., Jr., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wessel, Theodore J., Undated (Box 31)
  - West McLean - No Tresspassing Signs, Undated (Box 31)
  - West, E. Joseph, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Westgate - Flow General Office Building, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Westgate - Garfield Office Building, Undated (Box 31)
  - Westgate - Van Buren Office Building, Undated (Box 31)
  - Westgate - Westpark Office Building, Undated (Box 31)
  - Westpark, Undated (Box 31)
  - Weyl, Nancy, Undated (Box 31)
  - Whalen, Frank D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wheeler, Laurence, Undated (Box 31)
  - Whipple, William B., Undated (Box 31)
  - White, Betty S., Undated (Box 31)
  - White, Donald F., Undated (Box 31)
  - White, Elizabeth S., 1988 (Box 31)
  - White, Justice Byron, 1987 (Box 31)
  - White, M.P., Undated (Box 31)
  - White, Margita Eklund, Undated (Box 31)
  - White, Marilyn, Undated (Box 31)
  - White, Michael Stuart, Undated (Box 31)
  - White, W. Edward, Undated (Box 31)
  - Whitener, Steven, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Whitesel, Mindy, Undated (Box 31)
  - Whitesides, William L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Whitlock, Kenneth, Undated (Box 31)
  - Whitmer, Julian K., Undated (Box 31)
  - Whitmore, Harold B., Undated (Box 31)
  - Whitson, Bruce, Undated (Box 31)
  - Whyte, Joseph L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wigger, G. Eugene, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wilder, Gov. Lawrence Douglas, 1992 (Box 31)
  - Wilhelmi, Charlotte, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wilkes, George B. IV, Undated (Box 31)
  - Willard, Marjorie, Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Carrington, Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Earle, Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Glenn S.K., Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Harley M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Randolph, Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Robert E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, Thomas E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Williams, William A., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Willoughby, Clyde M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Willson, William N., Jr., 1964 (Box 31)
  - Wilson, Edith G., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Wilson, Kenneth R., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wilson, Linda, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wilson, Patricia, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Wilson, Robert W., 1973 (Box 31)
  - Wiltshire, Barbara, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wimbish, R. Allen, Undated (Box 31)
  - Windstorm '89 damage, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Wineland, Dr. Robert A., Undated (Box 31)
  - Winslow, Darrell G., Undated (Box 31)
  - Winton, Walter F., Jr., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wirthlin, Richard B., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Wol, Erik, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wolf Trap - The Barns, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wolf Trap - Duke Ellington at construction site, 1971 (Box 31)
  - Wolf Trap - Filene Cente construction, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Wolf Trap - Log Cabin, 1993 (Box 31)
  - Wolf, Frank, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Woman's Club of McLean - Juanita Jackson, Virginia Lang, Martha Darby, 1991 February 16 (Box 31)
  - Wong, Michael C., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wood, David C., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wood, John H., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Wood, Tim, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wood, Walter A., III, Undated (Box 31)
  - Woodall, John E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Woodlea Mill sign, Undated (Box 31)
  - Woods, Ginger, Undated (Box 31)
  - Woods, Robert C., Undated (Box 31)
  - Woods, Thomas H., Undated (Box 31)
  - Woodside Lake, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Woodward, William B., 1981 (Box 31)
  - Wooldridge, James D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wooldridge, Robert W., Jr., 1995 (Box 31)
  - Wootten, Anita, Undated (Box 31)
  - Worthington, Virginia, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wrenn, Sue, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Wright, Dr. Brian, 1992 (Box 31)
  - Wright, Frances S., 1986 (Box 31)
  - Wright, J. Grant, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wright, Linda, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Wright, Dr. Robert D., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wright, Steven, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Wright, Susan L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wright, Dr. Thomas M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wurglitz, Alfred M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wuriu, Lisa, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wyatt, Barbara, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wyatt, Todd, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Wyles, Barbara, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Yap, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 31)
  - Yaremchuk, Karen E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Yates, Philip G., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Yearout, Becky, Undated (Box 31)
  - Yerks, Austin, Undated (Box 31)
  - Yerks, Austin J., Jr., Undated (Box 31)
  - Yevich, Robert H., 1983 (Box 31)
  - Yoh, Bernard, Undated (Box 31)
  - Yorkdale, Alan H., 1982 (Box 31)
  - Young, Ira S., 1989 (Box 31)
  - Young, Nathaniel F., Undated (Box 31)
  - Young, Robert, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Young, Thomas A., Undated (Box 31)
  - Young, Thomas N., 1983 (Box 31)
  - Younger, Eleanor C., Undated (Box 31)
  - Yount, Rev. George H., Undated (Box 31)
  - Yunker, Karl, Undated (Box 31)
  - Yuras, Richard J., Undated (Box 31)
  - Zalokar, Robert H., Undated (Box 31)
  - Zanfagna, Philip, Undated (Box 31)
  - Zeavin, Bernard H., 1984 (Box 31)
  - Zeiner, William E., 1984 (Box 31)
  - Zicht, Eric E., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Zillian, Patricia, Undated (Box 31)
  - Zimmet, Dr. Steven M., 1984 (Box 31)
  - Zinnamon, Arthur, Undated (Box 31)
  - Zobel, Adm. William, Undated (Box 31)
  - Zraket, Charles A., 1986 (Box 31)
  - Zumwalt, Adm. Elmo "Bud", Undated (Box 31)
  - Zung, Madeline, Undated (Box 31)